question_data = [
    {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car,"
             " you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament,"
             " you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
    ]
question_data2 = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "American rapper Dr. Dre actually has a Ph.D. doctorate.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"category": "Art", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Vincent van Gogh cut off one of his ears.", "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The United States was a member of the League of Nations.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "According to Greek Mythology, Zeus can control lightning.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The Japanese god Izanagi successfully returned his wife Izanami from the Underworld.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Oxford University is older than the Aztec Empire. ",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Like his character in &quot;Parks and Recreation&quot;, Aziz Ansari was born in South Carolina.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Donald Duck played the role of Bob Cratchit in Disney&#039;s 1983 adaptation of A Christmas Carol.",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Night on Bald Mountain was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney&#039;s 1940&#039;s film Fantasia.",
      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "NCIS stands for &quot;Navy Corps Investigative Service&quot;",
      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
